# **Adam Lang**

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# **Profile**

My name is Adam Lang and I moved to Israel from Sweden in 2022. I have a technical background where I studied mobile application development but have since then transitioned into a web developer and I am now in the pursuit of a career in high tech in Israel. I have 6 months of experience as a front end developer at a cutting edge company in Sweden.

# **Employment History**

## Logistics Handler, Kibbutz Tzuba, Jerusalem

OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Receive and inspect food deliveries from suppliers.
- Organize all the products according to the FIFO principle.
- Handled the logistics of picking up and delivering items.
- I handle inventory to ensure that the correct amount and product is ordered.

### Junior Software Developer, Animech AB, Uppsala

SEPTEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2021

- Front end developer with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Rebuilt Animech's internal website from an old code base into a new React website reducing the number of files by 10%.
- Effectively multi tasked and worked with 2 internal teams in order to complete assigned project.
- Designed and coded new software or modified existing software to add new features.

# Education

## Stockholms Tekniska Institut, Stockholm

SEPTEMBER 2018 - MAY 2020

Mobile application development.

# **Internships**

#### Mobile app developer, MyIndicators, Stockholm

SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

Played a part in a project that was supposed to help the population increase their health and lifespan by not using addictive substances such as cigarettes and alcohol.

# Software Developer, Exor IT, Uppsala

FEBRUARY 2020 - APRIL 2020

Worked on an internal time schedule system that was meant to assist employers to keep a track of time spent at the office.

### **Details**

Israel 0534300361 adam.lang-1@hotmail.com

### Links

**Portfolio** 

## **Skills**

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

React

Git

GitHub

Restful API

Agile and Scrum

# Languages

Swedish

English

Hebrew